Guide to the Everett Education Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- United Teachers of Everett records, circa 1971-1986; 1973-1986; 3849-002; 22.00 cubic feet
  - Grievance Procedures and Forms, Undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Grievances- Bayes, Jackson, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Grievance: Violation of Collective Bargaining Agreement, Membership Communications, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Greg Nelson Grievance Case, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Annette Barca Class Size Grievance Complaint, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Annette Barca Exclusivity and Access Grievances, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Annette Barca Sick Leave Policy Grievance, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Annette Barca Leave Denial Grievance, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Carol Ransick Grievance- Denied Leave, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Luverne Sorenson Grievance- Requested Transfer, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Rich Stewart Case, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Virginia Sundal Grievance, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Stanley Tesdahl Grievance, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - John Tsuru Grievance, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Unassigned Status Teachers (Storano, Lybyer, Belcher, Barney, Mizrahi, Morrison, Cotes), 1975 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Shirley Walthall, Undated (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Barbara Wise Grievance- Denial of Sabbatical, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Alison Wysong Argument and Grievance, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Don D'Andrea Case- Injured Child, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Merrilee Howard Title IX Supplemental Contract Grievance, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Helen Hull Grievance- Salary Placement, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Mike Irons Grievance- Salary Placement, 1972-1976 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - David Kosche Grievance- Salary Placement, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Strike Related Personal Losses, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Subpoena Leave Grievance- Linda Vail, Donna Linden, Harold McNeil and Warren Hewett, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Substitute Grievances Re: Strike, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Wartelle Grievance re: Contract and Reduction in Force List, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Steve Bennett Evaluation, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Mel Nokleby Discipline Grievance, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Gail Svitil Grievance- Salary Determination, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - EAPE Grievance, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Michael Rainey- Resolution of Contract Grievance, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Retroactive Pay Arbitration, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Helen Hull Arbitration, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Salary Schedule Placement Arbitration- Karen Hansen, Shelley Mizrahi, Nancy Linda Butler, Jeff Solomon, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Subpoena Leave Arbitration, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Unfair Labor Practices Complaint, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Possible Grievances- Therapy, Adoption, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Misc. Grievances, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Millikan/Peterson Grievance Re: Academic Freedom, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Patti Barney Grievance- Placement, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Kathy Deller Grievance- Preference for Opening, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Leslie Elaesser Grievance- Duty Schedule, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Experience Credit Case, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Grievance - Steven Jones, James Kyle, Judith Romaneschi, Maureen Osgood, Shirley Moses- Experience Salary Credits, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Kathleen Harris Maternity Case, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Stephanie Haskins Grievance- Transfer, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Theresa Hoder Grievance, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Individual Insurance Question, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Al Kaminski Case, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Lyle Messinger Absence Grievance Case, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Gordon Millikan Grievance Case- Summer Workshop, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Val Boyce Grievance, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Gordon Millikan Grievance Violation of Contract, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Waldon Anderson Performance Evaluation, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Anne King Grievance- 1982 Evaluation and Non-Renewal of Contract, 1982-1973 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Cassette Tape: Russ Rebel (Mrs. North), Undated; Cassette Tape (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Financial Records, 1972-1978 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Bills Paid, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Records of Paid Dues, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Contract Deposit Form and Trust Agreement, Undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Application for Financial Assistance from the Washington Education Association, Undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Washington Education Association Cancellation forms for APA, Undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Washington Education Association Change of Personal Data Form, Undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Dues Structure and Fees/Lists, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Everett Education Association Enrollment Forms, Undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Payroll Deduction and Dues Information, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Pulse/National Education Association PAC Option Form (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Grievance Forms and Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Washington Education Association- Assistance and Action Fund Guidelines and Forms, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Scrapbook: Newspaper Clippings Especially Re: Teachers Strike, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Scrapbook: Newspaper Clippings Especially Re: Bond Levy, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Scrapbook: Newspaper Clippings Especially Re: School Board Elections, Bus Strike and Levy, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - By-Laws and Revisions, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Representative Council Minutes and Agendas, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Executive Board Minutes and Agendas, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - General Membership Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Executive Board Meetings With Superintendent Minutes and Agendas, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Everett Education Association Budget Reports, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Convention, Evaluations, Negotiation Information, Project Priority, Other Administrative Paperwork, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Council Recommendations for Negotiations, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Negotiation Proposals by Everett Education Association to Everett School District Board of Directors, Agreements, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Leadership Workbook, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board Minutes and Agendas, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Representative Council Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Executive Board Minutes, Agendas, Negotiations, By-Laws, Leadership Handbook, etc., 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Executive Board/Bargaining Contacts, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Representative Council Agendas and Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Executive Board Contacts, Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Everett Education Association Budget Reports, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Contract Development Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Community Newsletter Development Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Political Unity of Leaders in State Education PAC, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Community Action Committee Contacts, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Everett Education Association and Political Unity of Leaders in State Education Membership, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Pilchuck Unisev Council's Instruction and Professional Development Committee, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Everett Education Association By-Laws, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Contract and Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1978-1980 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Executive Board Agendas, Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Representative Council Minutes and Agendas, 1981-1983 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Everett Education Association Budget Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Executive Board Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Documents Re: Public and Other Unions, PATCO, Membership, 1981-1982 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - "The Educator" Publication, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Organizational Structure, 1980-1981 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Executive Board and Superintendent Meetings and Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Executive Board, Political Action Representatives, Building Representative Rosters, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Political Public Disclosure Reports and Documents, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Public Announcements, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - PAC Meeting minutes, Notes, Budget, By-Laws, 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Political Reference Information, Organizing Handbook, Contacts and Initiative 363, 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Community Survey, Undated (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Washington Education Association Lobbying Manual, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - PAC Meeting Activity, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Everett Education Association PAC Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - PAC By-Laws, Undated (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - PAC- Pilchuck Uniserv Council Political Action, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Everett Education Association PAC Political Activity, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Political Action Bills and Expenses, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Oversized Box (Box 21 Oversized)
  - General Correspondence and Union Notices, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Communications with other Labor Organizations, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - United Teachers of Everett Labor Caucus Budget, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Everett Federation of Teachers- AFL-CIO, National Education Association, Washington Education Association and Washington State Labor Council, 1977-1982 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Washington Federation of Teachers- National Education Association debate over AFL-CIO, 1979-1980 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Resolutions and Amendments to the Washington State Labor Council Constitution, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Materials from Washington State Labor Council Convention- Pamphlets, History, Newspapers, and Constitutions and Resolutions, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - American Federation of Teachers Executive Council Proceedings and Newsletters, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - AFL-CIO Affiliates' Newsletters, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - NEA Organizing/Membership Newsletters, Constitution of Everett Federation of Teachers, etc., 1976-1981 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Labor Caucus Membership List, Undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Everett Education Association vs. Everett Federation of Teachers- EFT Materials, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Everett Federation of Teachers Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Everett Federation of Teachers- Press Releases, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Everett Federation of Teachers- Everett Education Association Strike, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Everett Federation of Teachers Strike- Documents, Fliers, etc., 1976 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Everett Federation of Teachers- Fliers and Newsletters, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Everett Federation of Teachers- Correspondence, esp. with Washington State Labor Council, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Washington Federation of Teachers- minutes, notes, activity reports, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Resigning/Retiring Teachers and Recall Correspondence with Everett School District, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Solidarity Day, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Washington Federation of Teachers- HB 166 Salary Lid, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - American Federation of Teachers- ACTION Newsletter, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - American Federation of Teachers- Constitution and By-Laws, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - American Federation of Teachers - Auto Insurance- Coverage/Discounts, 1969-1972 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - American Federation of Teachers- Insurance Plans, 1972-1977 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Mutual of Omaha Insurance- Salary Insurance, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Liability Insurance Plans, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Labor Caucus Officers, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Legislative Contacts, Information, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - United Teachers of Everett Labor Caucus Constitution, Undated (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Everett Federation of Teachers Membership Drive, Undated (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Snohomish Country Labor Council Labeletter, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Everett Federation of Teachers New Delegates Correspondence, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Washington State Labor Council Report, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Washington State Labor Council - Directory of Affiliates and Committees, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Various Labor Organization Newsletters, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Effects of HB 166, Delegate Housing Info, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - "Everett Teacher" Publication by Everett Federation of Teachers, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Everett Education Association records, circa 1966-1974; 3849-003; .28 cubic foot
  Program materials, memos, minutes, agreements.
  Donated by the Association, 3/9/1987.
  - ORGANIZATIONAL MATERIALS, 1970-1973; SERIES I (Box-folder 1/1-1/6)
    - Constitution and Bylaws, 1972 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Proposed Amendments for Constitution and Bylaws, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Leadership Handbook (Part 1 of 2), 1971-1973 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Leadership Handbook (Part 2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Professional Agreement Between Board of Directors Everett School District No. 2 and Everett Education Association, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Proposed Master Contract Between Everett School District Board of Directors and Everett Education Association, 1972 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - FINANCIAL MATERIAL, 1971-1974; SERIES II (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Financial Materials (includes Budget, 4-Year Levy Plan, Tax Reform Proposal Defeat Statement), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - COMMITTEES AND CHARGES/NEGOTIATIONS, 1970-1974; SERIES III (Box-folder 1/8-1/15)
    - Executive Board and Representative Council, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Charges and Negotiations, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Improvement of Instruction Committee (Part 1 of 4), 1966-1971 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - Improvement of Instruction Committee (Part 2 of 4), 1970-1973 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Improvement of Instruction Committee (Part 3 of 4), 1971-1972 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - Improvement of Instruction Committee (Part 4 of 4), 1972 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Ad Hoc Committees (Ad Hoc Class Size Committee, Ad Hoc Planning Time Committee), 1973 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Correspondence: Committee Chairmen, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 1/15)
  - SUBSTITUTES/TEACHERS' AIDES, 1972-1973; SERIES IV (Box-folder 1/16)
    - Teaching Assistants and Aides (Includes Guidelines, "Thoughts on Substituting", Salary Proposals), 1972-1973 (Box-folder 1/16)
  - CLASSROOM MATERIALS, 1966-1967; SERIES V (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Textbook and Supplementary Books/Materials Policies, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 1/17)
- United Teachers of Everett records, 1986-1990; 3849-004; 1.61 cubic feet
  Correspondence, surveys, reports, dues files, membership files, budget files, resolutions, conferences and conventions, cartoon, logo design, subject series.
  Donated by Carol Schramm, 2/5/1992.
  - Q And A On Wages, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 1/1)
  - National Education Association Committee And Financial Report, 1989 (Box-folder 1/2)
  - National Education Association Legislative Agenda, 1989 (Box-folder 1/3)
  - National Education Association. Budgets, Part 1 of 4, 1989 (Box-folder 1/4)
  - National Education Association. Budgets, Part 2 of 4, 1988 (Box-folder 1/5)
  - National Education Association. Budgets, Part 3 of 4, 1989 (Box-folder 1/6)
  - National Education Association. Budgets, Part 4 of 4, 1987 (Box-folder 1/7)
  - National Education Association - Programs And Services, 1989 (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Constitution Of The National Education Association, 1981 (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Article "Nuclear Navy", Undated (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Political Action, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 1/11)
  - Everett School's Shower Procedure And Policy, 1989 (Box-folder 1/12)
  - Special Education, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 1/13)
  - National Association Special Service Award, Undated (Box-folder 1/14)
  - Substitute Teachers, 1981-1987 (Box-folder 1/15)
  - Highlights of Tax Changes, 1986 (Box-folder 1/16)
  - United Food and Commercial Workers Strike Info, 1989 (Box-folder 1/17)
  - Report On The Constitutional Convention Of The AFL-CIO, 1985 (Box-folder 1/18)
  - Inventory Tax Report, 1984 (Box-folder 1/19)
  - YMCA Investment In Youth, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 1/20)
  - American Education Week Resource Guide, 1989 (Box-folder 1/21)
  - Cascade High School Letter, 1988 (Box-folder 1/22)
  - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Phone Chains, Undated (Box-folder 1/23)
  - National Teacher Day Proclamation From Bill Moore And Wills Tucker, 1989 (Box-folder 1/24)
  - Special Services, Undated (Box-folder 1/25)
  - SPI (Communications) Goals For Washington Public Schools, 1985 (Box-folder 1/26)
  - Washington Education Association Bargaining Information, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 1/27)
  - School Effectiveness Surveys, 1988 (Box-folder 1/28)
  - National Education Association/Washington Education Association Delegate Forms, 1989 (Box-folder 1/29)
  - Washington State Economic Development, 1987 (Box-folder 1/30)
  - Youth Resource Center Relocation And School Plan, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 1/31)
  - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Goals, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 1/32)
  - Blue Cross and Washington Education Association Insurance Information, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 1/33)
  - Union Teacher Press Association Workshop "Heads and Headlines", 1984 (Box-folder 1/34)
  - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Dues Information and Member Enrollment Guide, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 1/35)
  - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Phone And Meeting Log, 1985 (Box-folder 1/36)
  - Herald Strike Information, 1988 (Box-folder 1/37)
  - Washington Education Association Uniserv Program, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 1/38)
  - RAP Program Survey, 1988 (Box-folder 1/39)
  - Project Merge For Garfield Elementary, Undated (Box-folder 1/40)
  - Jefferson Elementary Notes On Optional Days, Undated (Box-folder 1/41)
  - Washington Education Association Legal Policies and Court Cases Part 1 of 2, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 1/42)
  - Washington Education Association Legal Policies and Court Cases Part 2 of 2, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 1/43)
  - Everett Middle School Accreditation Report 1985-1986, 1988 (Box-folder 1/44)
  - Everett School District Middle School Staffing, 1988 (Box-folder 1/45)
  - District Staff Development Committee Building Representatives and Mission Statement, 1984 (Box-folder 1/46)
  - Article "Illiteracy: It's not all discouraging words", 1989 (Box-folder 1/47)
  - Resolution in Support of BPA Zero Rate Increase, Undated (Box-folder 1/48)
  - Requirements for the Allocation and Election of Delegates to the National Education Association Representative Assembly, 1986 (Box-folder 1/49)
  - Strike Sanctions, 1987 (Box-folder 1/50)
  - Class Size Survey and Effective School Plans, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 1/51)
  - Everett Education Association Poster, Undated (Box-folder 2/1)
  - Insurance Pooling Information, 1984 (Box-folder 2/2)
  - Insurance Coverage and Costs, 1984 (Box-folder 2/3)
  - Changes to Insurance Plans, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 2/4)
  - Washington Education Association Sponsored Insurance Plans, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 2/5)
  - Everett School District and Everett Education Association Joint Insurance Committee Health Plan Analysis, 1985 (Box-folder 2/6)
  - Meeting Attendance Sheets, Undated (Box-folder 2/7)
  - President's Release Time Surveys, 1990 (Box-folder 2/8)
  - Carnegie Decision-Making Report, 1988 (Box-folder 2/9)
  - Child Abuse Legislation, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 2/10)
  - Child Care Referral/Resource Service, 1985 (Box-folder 2/11)
  - Initiative 102 Information and Voters Pamphlet, 1989 (Box-folder 2/12)
  - Children's Initiative, 1989 (Box-folder 2/13)
  - Impact of Early Release Days on Coaching Schedule Survey, 1988 (Box-folder 2/14)
  - Evergreen Middle School Goal Setting and Special Education Program, 1989 (Box-folder 2/15)
  - Garfield Elementary Air Circulation, 1987 (Box-folder 2/16)
  - Carol Hamilton Complaint of Communication, 1988 (Box-folder 2/17)
  - Hawthorne Elementary Booklet and School Plan, 1985 (Box-folder 2/18)
  - Human Relations Part 1 of 2, 1983 (Box-folder 2/19)
  - Human Relations Part 2 of 2, 1983 (Box-folder 2/20)
  - School Calendar Vote, 1988 (Box-folder 2/21)
  - Library Cataloging Changes, 1988 (Box-folder 2/22)
  - Music Budget Proposal, 1988 (Box-folder 2/23)
  - Fluoride Debate, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 2/24)
  - Class Size Information, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 2/25)
  - Mike Sells, Letter about Lack of Teacher Pay Raise, 1987 (Box-folder 2/26)
  - Grievances and Complaints from D. Rosenthal, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 2/27)
  - Late Day Start Poll, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 2/28)
  - Madison School Concerns, 1987 (Box-folder 2/29)
  - More Effective School Plan and Accomplishments, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 2/30)
  - Teachers Out-of-Pocket Expenses, 1986 (Box-folder 2/31)
  - Woodside Early Report Card Release Comments, 1988 (Box-folder 2/32)
  - Woodside Comments on Moving Day for Transfer to New Buildings, 1988 (Box-folder 2/33)
  - Class Size Survey, 1987 (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Elementary Self-Study Survey, 1989 (Box-folder 2/35)
  - Class Size Survey and Note, Undated (Box-folder 2/36)
  - Governor's Committee on Washington's Financial Future, 1988 (Box-folder 2/37)
  - Washington Federation of Teachers and Washington State Labor Council Special Committee on Political Education Convention Nominations, 1988 (Box-folder 2/38)
  - Everett Education Association and United Teachers of Everett Goals, 1987 (Box-folder 2/39)
  - 1986-'87 Calendar Bargaining (Box-folder 2/40)
  - R.S.V.P. Forms, 1989 (Box-folder 2/41)
  - Washington Federation of Teachers Convention Ballots, 1989 (Box-folder 2/42)
  - Everett Education Association Membership Lists, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 2/43)
  - New Members, 1986 (Box-folder 2/44)
  - Everett Education Association Membership List and Dues Information, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 2/45)
  - Everett Education Association Dues Distribution Forms- '84, 1984 (Box-folder 2/46)
  - Everett Education Association Dues Distribution Forms- '83, 1983 (Box-folder 2/47)
  - Everett Education Association Membership Cancellations '85-'86, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 2/48)
  - Everett Education Association Membership Cancellations '84-'85, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 2/49)
  - Everett Education Association Membership Cancellations '82-'83, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 2/50)
  - Membership List '80-'83, 1980-1984 (Box-folder 2/51)
  - Membership List and Dues '81-'82, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 2/52)
  - Membership List '82-'83, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 2/53)
  - Membership List and Dues '80-'81, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2/54)
  - Committee on Political Education Endorsing Convention Nominations, 1987 (Box-folder 2/55)
  - ''87-'88 Nomination Forms, 1987 (Box-folder 2/56)
  - ''85-'86 Nomination Forms, 1985 (Box-folder 2/57)
  - W.F.T Convention Ballots, 1987 (Box-folder 2/58)
  - Wartelle Unemployment Benefits Lawsuit Information, 1987 (Box-folder 2/59)
  - Black Armband Day Survey Results, 1989 (Box-folder 2/60)
  - Notes and Report on Informal Bargaining, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 2/61)
  - Kindergarten Committee, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 2/62)
  - Evergreen Petitions, 1988 (Box-folder 2/63)
  - Walkout Information and Feedback, Undated (Box-folder 2/64)
  - Second Uniserv Director Issue and Report, 1986 (Box-folder 2/65)
  - Northwest Regional Workshop, 1987 (Box-folder 2/66)
  - Long-Term Substitutes, 1983 (Box-folder 2/67)
  - Labor Caucus Committee on Political Education Convention Ballots, 1988 (Box-folder 2/68)
  - Membership Feedback Form, Undated (Box-folder 2/69)